Mariam SolimanHanna

01285587822

in mariam.soliman.hanna@gmail.com

in/mariam-soliman

Address: Maryotia,, Giza, Egypt

Date of birthday: 15 April 1990

Summary

Through time, our way of thinking changes. We become more mature and deeper in developing ourselves and the challenge of changing the problems that face us and the way to deal with them professionally. This is life's experience, the challenge of success and continuing to achieve ourselves.

Education

Cairo University, Faculty of pharmacy

(2007 - 2012)

Bachelor's degree in pharmacy

Grade: good.

Sadat University faculty of pharmacy

Grad: excellent Diploma in Clinical nutrition

Scope Certification

Work Experience

- Pharmacies from august 2012 in a public pharmacies so I have experience in talking skills and other skills in facing problems to may 2014
- IN Queen international company as a medical representative on Pediatric products then product assistant manger from June 2014 till may 2017
- Pharmacies from June 2017 till August 2018
- IN Chemipharm Company from 1/9/2018 pediatrics line as supervisor till 12/2020.
- Online Nutrition specialist from 1/2020 till now with achieved goals for many patients

Courses

- Sales, Marketing & Communication Skills: by Eva Company in summer training courses.
- Mangment of infectious diseases accredited by SKAGGS school of pharmacy & pharmaceuticals siences university of COLORADO

ANSCHUTZ MEDICAL CAMPUS, online course

- Online courses in nutrition basics and how to manage Obesity
- Photo-shop ,illustration diploma in Russian Culture Center

Languages

• Arabic: Native

• English: V .Good written , spoken& reading

• French: Good written & fair spoken

Computer Skills

• Microsoft Office: Excellent in Word , Power Point & Excel

• Internet use& Mail: Excellent

Additional Personal Skills.

- Flexible for learning anything new
- Self motivated
- Creative & effective communicator
- Responsible
- Hard Worker

References:

references and transcripts are furnished upon request.